

KONRAD KORABIOWSKI



kkorabiowski@gmail.com



+48



Warszawa

SUMMARY

I'm engineer who isn't glad with previous career as a HVAC systems designer and decided to change path of career. I don't have any commercial experience doing web apps or websites but I want to change it. I can make simple to-do apps, sliders, shopping carts etc. in Javascript. I have basic knowledge

of using webpack, npm and node.js and git. I also used contentful and netlify. Now I'm learning React.js, next - Redux. In the future I see myself as a professional Front-End Developer / Full-Stack Developer, step by step I realize my plan. By joining your company, I'm committing to make myself and my job the best as I can.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dec 2017 - Apr 2018

HVAC installation designer

MagInstal / Warsaw

- + Making documentation and technical drawings in AutoCad program.
- + Designing HVAC systems
- + Overview households and multi-occupied buildings

Jul 2016 - Jul 2017

Designing office KOMA

Gas systems engineer

- + Making documentation and technical drawings in AutoCad program.
- + Designing gas systems
- + Overview households and multi-occupied buildings

EDUCATION

2017 - 2019

Warsaw University of Technology

M.Sc. in Environmental

Engineering

- + Faculty: "Wydział Instalacji Budowlanych, Hydrotechniki i Inżynierii Środowiska"
- + Environmental Engineering
- + Spec.: Heating, Ventilation and Air Conditioning Systems
- + Master Science degree

2013 - 2017

Poznań University of Technology

B.E in Evironmental

Engineering

- + Faculty: "Wydział Budownictwa i Inżynierii Środowiska"
- + Environmental Engineering
- + Engineer degree

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSSSASS
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- React
- •••••

.

SOFTWARE

- VS Code
- AutoCAD
- Photoshop
- Windows
- MS Office
- ••••••
- •••••
- e ••••••••

LANGUAGES

- English (B2)
- · Polish (native)

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Ability to achieving goals
- Ability to multi-task
- Attention to detail
- Dependability
- Self-motivation

INTERESTS

- Financial books
- Physics
- Graphic design
- Psychology
- Sport

FOLLOW ME

- linkedin.com/konrad-korabiowski
- github.com/kkorab

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)"